ATSUKI KITADA

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT

236-838-1813

✓ canvanvam@gmail.com

Q Vancouver, BC

https://atsukiii.com

EDUCATION

College

2023 - Present Cornerstone International Community College of Canada Diploma of Computer Science

University

2015 - 2019 Doshisha University Bachelor's in Law

SKILLS

LANGUAGES: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Typescript

FRAMEWORKS, LIBRARIES:

NodeJs, ReactJS, NextJS, React Router, Redux, Bootstrap, SASS, TailwindCSS, Framer Motion

OTHERS: Supabase, Git, Figma, Canva

PROFILE

I am a passionate web developer with a strong curiosity for technology and a keen eye for creating beautiful and functional websites. My drive for creativity, problemsolving, and continuous learning sets me apart. I am enthusiastic about contributing my skills and expertise to help businesses and individuals achieve their goals. Let's collaborate to bring your ideas to life and create exceptional web experiences that leave a lasting impression.

WORK EXPERIENCE

ADMINISTRATIVE OFFICER

Civil Aviation Bureau - Accounting Department

April 2019 - March 2021

- Managed financial and administrative tasks within the accounting department.
- Ensured accuracy and compliance with financial procedures.

Civil Aviation Bureau - Human Resources department *April 2021 - December 2022*

- Led the management of the mutual benefit association for over 6000 employees.
- Oversaw the issuance of insurance cards and verified employees' eligibility for insurance coverage.
- Promoted to team leader, effectively managing and training a team of employees.